

Dimitri Lyomin

Front-End Developer

Penza, Russia

Personal profile

I'm a Front-End developer with 5+ years of experience. I create, develop and maintain websites from plain markups to high-loaded, scalable and performant SPA. I'm responsible, reliable, flexible and well-organized. I work well with others and I value and respect time constraints and deadlines.

I am also great with clients: when a client has a question, I take the time to explain and clarify our process to them in an appropriate way.

Professional experience

Front-End Developer, Purchasing Platform, LLC, Chicago, USA

June 2018 - Present

- Developed, improved SPA created with React + MobX
- Covered code via e2e tests with Cypress
- Code review

Front-End Developer, EastWood, Penza, Russia

March 2015 - May 2018

- Developed, maintained and improved SPA working with Transparency.js
- Created and implemented use of Unit Tests with Karma and Jasmine
- Built mobile version application
- Improved rendering time characteristics of application
- Middle management, assigned tasks among team
- Code review
- Developed and improved custom architecture SPA created with native JS

Front-End Developer, Q-Cis, Moscow, Russia

February 2014 - February 2015

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Developed, maintained and improved SPA based on AngularJS
- Created markup application with LESS and Bootstrap

Front-End Developer, Crowd Lab, Moscow, Russia

March 2013 - September 2013

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Developed, maintained and improved SPA with AngularJS
- Developed and improved markup application with Stylus

Front-End Developer / Back-End Developer, Freelance, Moscow, Russia / Kiev, Ukraine

October 2012 - February 2013

- Built responsive and adaptive websites
- Maintained and improved back end with php

Front-End Developer, Popel Studio, Kiev, Ukraine

September 2011 - September 2012

- · Built and improved custom websites with Joomla, Wordpress, Kohana
- Maintained and improved back end with php



¿? lyomin.com





github.com/lemind

Expertise & Core Skills

Development

- JavaScript, HTML, jQuery
- · CSS (Less, Sass, Stylus), BEM, Bootstrap

State Management

Redux, Vuex, MobX

Testing

- · Jest, Enzume
- · Karma, Jasmine
- Cypress

Workflow

- · Git, Webpack
- · Docker, Heroku, Travis

Back-End

· Node.js, Express, Mongo

Project Management

· Agile, Jira, Pivotal, Remove Working

Basic Knowledge

Angular2, TypeScript, RxJS

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science Penza State University

2001-2006

Specialization in Engineering: Automatic System of Information Processing and Managing

Languages

Russian - Native English - Intermediate